<?xml version="1.0" encoding="utf-8"?><feed xmlns="http://www.w3.org/2005/Atom" ><generator uri="https://jekyllrb.com/" version="3.8.5">Jekyll</generator><link href="http://auburn-barleria-fc6e.siteleaf.net/feed.xml" rel="self" type="application/atom+xml" /><link href="http://auburn-barleria-fc6e.siteleaf.net/" rel="alternate" type="text/html" /><updated>2022-04-07T07:25:43+00:00</updated><id>http://auburn-barleria-fc6e.siteleaf.net/feed.xml</id><title type="html">A Night in Japan</title><subtitle>A blog about Japan</subtitle><entry><title type="html">Everybody wears Supreme</title><link href="http://auburn-barleria-fc6e.siteleaf.net/2022/04/06/welcome-to-jekyll.html" rel="alternate" type="text/html" title="Everybody wears Supreme" /><published>2022-04-06T00:00:00+00:00</published><updated>2022-04-06T00:00:00+00:00</updated><id>http://auburn-barleria-fc6e.siteleaf.net/2022/04/06/welcome-to-jekyll</id><content type="html" xml:base="http://auburn-barleria-fc6e.siteleaf.net/2022/04/06/welcome-to-jekyll.html">&lt;p&gt;One of the five supreme stores is located in omotensando in harajuku, Tokyo, and this store is a smaller one in Tokyo comparing with the other one in &lt;strong&gt;Shibuya&lt;/strong&gt;. If you have viewed my last article about goro’s which is also in omotensando, this supreme is exactly close to the goro’s. You just have to turn left into the a narrow street as you see goro’s and a smart red logo saying, &lt;a href=&quot;https://www.supremenewyork.com/&quot;&gt;“supreme”&lt;/a&gt; will show up. It is one the second floor based on the black neighbourhood clothing store. I went upstairs and step in the store and a strong feeling of skateboarding culture impressed me a lot. There was a big screen always playing skateboarding videos and a huge arc light was in the right corner of the shop. The staffs is normally friendly to you, while staffs in Shibuya got a worse attitude to travelers.&lt;/p&gt;

&lt;p&gt;Supreme items normally drop at 11 am local time every Saturday in Japan, so if you are interested in supreme and you are coincidentally in Japan, try your luck to queue for the drop one might before Saturday which is Friday. It is gonna be a time consuming event, but it’s one of the typical properties fashion event in Japan. There would be staffs adjust the teams into different sections at the Friday night, and some people lucky who get a small number(there would be draw before the line up) can get in the store preferentially. You can get some hyped  items if you are least than 200, but it depends on what supreme are releasing that week, some most hyped items gone pretty fast as it dropped.&lt;/p&gt;

&lt;h2 id=&quot;what-else&quot;&gt;What else?&lt;/h2&gt;

&lt;p&gt;Believe me, queuing can almost represent Japanese people attitude to life such that order is the most important rule to follow. However, if you go there not in the period of season, there are actually no many good stuffs selling in store, for me, I just got a pack of 3 Hanes supreme tee for about 6000 yen, which is not a big deal but still decent. You can pay by credit card or cash, don’t worry about what type of payment supreme can’t do, they accept any payment.&lt;/p&gt;

&lt;p&gt;&lt;a href=&quot;https://www.tokyocreative.com/articles/19065-experience-in-supreme-harajuku-tokyo-and-osaka&quot;&gt;Read the full article here&lt;/a&gt;&lt;/p&gt;</content><author><name></name></author><summary type="html">One of the five supreme stores is located in omotensando in harajuku, Tokyo, and this store is a smaller one in Tokyo comparing with the other one in Shibuya.</summary></entry><entry><title type="html">All of the lights</title><link href="http://auburn-barleria-fc6e.siteleaf.net/2022/04/03/another-post.html" rel="alternate" type="text/html" title="All of the lights" /><published>2022-04-03T00:00:00+00:00</published><updated>2022-04-03T00:00:00+00:00</updated><id>http://auburn-barleria-fc6e.siteleaf.net/2022/04/03/another-post</id><content type="html" xml:base="http://auburn-barleria-fc6e.siteleaf.net/2022/04/03/another-post.html">&lt;p&gt;Blog content 2&lt;/p&gt;</content><author><name></name></author><summary type="html">The nightlife in Japan here runs the gamut, from rowdy izakayas and beer bars, to red-light entertainment and the infamous Robot Restaurant.</summary></entry><entry><title type="html">5 Tokyo train tips</title><link href="http://auburn-barleria-fc6e.siteleaf.net/2022/04/02/tokyo-train.html" rel="alternate" type="text/html" title="5 Tokyo train tips" /><published>2022-04-02T00:00:00+00:00</published><updated>2022-04-02T00:00:00+00:00</updated><id>http://auburn-barleria-fc6e.siteleaf.net/2022/04/02/tokyo-train</id><content type="html" xml:base="http://auburn-barleria-fc6e.siteleaf.net/2022/04/02/tokyo-train.html">&lt;p&gt;Blog content 3&lt;/p&gt;</content><author><name></name></author><summary type="html">Here are my five tips to keep you sane and get you to your destination on the Tokyo Subway.</summary></entry></feed>